A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1987-2003(2002-2003)
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files 1987-2003(2002-2003)
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-2/1/2.051
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access is prohibited for ten years from the date of creation unless special permission is granted by the President's Office. Under the terms of the Virginia Freedom of Information Act (Sec. 2.1-343 (4), the records of the president or other chief executive officer of any state-supported institution of higher education are exempt from the law's access provisions.
Additional access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
These records were transferred from the Office of the President, Madison Hall, University of Virginia, through Jo Anne Birckhead, on August 12, 2005.
Scope and Content
These files constitute the major record series generated by the president of the University of Virginia, John Thomas Casteen, 12,300 items (41 Hollinger boxes, ca. 17 linear shelf feet) chiefly 2002-2003, but with some files going back to 1987.
The records consist chiefly of correspondence, but also include reports, minutes, clippings, memoranda, and related papers concerning all areas of business of the president's office. Major topics include American Council on Education; Association of American Universities; athletics and the NCAA; the Council for Higher Education Accreditation; development, the General Assembly; gifts and grants; the Governor of Virginia's office; the Mariners' Museum; the Medical Center and the Health Services Foundation; ROTC; Sallie Mae; State Council of Higher Education for Virginia; Student Affairs; and the Board of Visitors.
Arrangement
Both the series and file headings used by the president's office have been retained. Restricted material has been placed in its own series. There are three series: Series I: General Files (Boxes 1-32); Series II: Seldom Used Permanent Files (Boxes 32-34); and, Series III: Restricted Files (Boxes 35-41).
Contents List
- Series I: General Files
  - "A-Al" Miscellaneous, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 1:1)
  - "Am-American J" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 1:2)
  - "American P-Ar" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 1:3)
  - "As-Ay" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 1:4)
  - African-American Affairs, 2002 Jul - 2003 May (Box-folder 1:5)
  - Alumni Association - General, 2002 Aug - 2003 June (Box-folder 1:6)
  - Alumni Association - Board of Managers, 2002 Jul - 2003 May (Box-folder 1:7)
  - American Bar Association, 2002 August - December (Box-folder 2:1)
  - American Council of Learned Societies, 2002 May - 2003 April (Box-folder 2:2)
  - American Council on Education - General, 2003 January - June (Box-folder 2:3)
  - American Council on Education - General, 2002 November - December (Box-folder 2:4)
  - American Council on Education - General, 2002 July- October (Box-folder 2:5)
  - American Council on Education- The Presidency, 2002 September - 2003 April (Box-folder 2:6)
  - American Institute of Certified Public Accountants, 2002 January - 2003 January (Box-folder 2:7)
  - Architecture, 2002 July - 2003 July (Box-folder 3:1)
  - Art- General, 2002 August - 2003 January (Box-folder 3:2)
  - Art- University of Virginia Art Museum, 2002 August - 2003 April (Box-folder 3:3)
  - Arts & Sciences, 2002 June - 2003 April (Box-folder 3:4)
  - Association of Academic Health Centers, 2002 October - 2003 May (Box-folder 3:5)
  - Association of American Colleges and Universities, 2003 March- May (Box-folder 3:6)
  - Association of American Colleges and Universities, 2002 October- 2003 January (Box-folder 3:7)
  - Association of American Colleges and Universities, 2001 December, 2002 September (Box-folder 3:8)
  - Association of American Universities, 2003 May- June (Box-folder 3:9)
  - Association of American Universities, 2003 April 13 - 19 (Box-folder 4:1)
  - Association of American Universities, 2003 April 13 - 19 (Box-folder 4:2)
  - Association of American Universities, 2003 March-April 11 (Box-folder 4:3)
  - Association of American Universities, 2002 December- 2003 February (Box-folder 4:4)
  - Association of American Universities, 2002 November (Box-folder 4:5)
  - Association of American Universities, 2002 October 20 - 31 (Box-folder 5:1)
  - Association of American Universities, 2002 October 20 - 23 (Box-folder 5:2)
  - Association of American Universities, 2002 September - October 17 (Box-folder 5:3)
  - Association of American Universities, 2002 July - August (Box-folder 5:4)
  - Association of Governing Boards, 2002 August-2003 June (Box-folder 5:5)
  - Athletics- General, 2002 September - 2003 June (Box-folder 5:6)
  - Athletics- Atlantic Coast Conference, 2002 November - 2003 June (Box-folder 6:1)
  - Athletics- Atlantic Coast Conference, 2002 September-October (Box-folder 6:2)
  - Athletics- Atlantic Coast Conference, 2002 July - August (Box-folder 6:3)
  - Athletics-National Collegiate Athletic Association, 2003 March - June (Box-folder 6:4)
  - Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association, 2002 November- 2003 February (Box-folder 6:5)
  - Athletics- National Collegiate Athletic Association, 2002 August - October (Box-folder 6:6)
  - Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association, 2002 July (Box-folder 7:1)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts (State), 2002 July-2003 February (Box-folder 7:2)
  - "Ba-Bi" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 7:3)
  - "Bl-Bo" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 7:4)
  - "Br" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 7:5)
  - "Bu-By" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 7:6)
  - Birdwood, 2002 September - 2003 February (Box-folder 7:7)
  - Blandy Experimental Farm, 2002 August - 2003 April (Box-folder 7:8)
  - Business and Finance, 2003 January - June (Box-folder 8:1)
  - Business and Finance, 2002 October - December (Box-folder 8:2)
  - Business and Finance, 2002 September (Box-folder 8:3)
  - Business and Finance, 2002 July (Box-folder 8:4)
  - "Cal-Cam" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 8:5)
  - "Can-Car" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 8:6)
  - "Cas-Centen" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 9:1)
  - "Center" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 9:2)
  - "Centr-Ch" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 9:3)
  - "Ci-Col" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 9:4)
  - "Com-Con" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 9:5)
  - "Coo-Cu" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 9:6)
  - Career Services- General, 2002 July - 2003 June (Box-folder 9:7)
  - Carilion Biomedical Institute, 2003 February-April (Box-folder 10:1)
  - Carilion Biomedical Institute, 2002 July - 2003 January (Box-folder 10:2)
  - Carnegie Corporation, 2002 May - 2003 March (Box-folder 10:3)
  - Carr's Hill, including plans for the kitchen (oversize), 2003 June (Box-folder 10:4)
  - Casteen, John T. III, 2002 July- 2003 June (Box-folder 10:5)
  - Cavalier Daily, 2003 March (Box-folder 10:6)
  - Charlottesville, City of - General, 2002 June - 2003 May (Box-folder 10:7)
  - Charlottesville, City of - Planning and Coordination Council, 2002 November - 2003 May (Box-folder 10:8)
  - College Board, 2002 July - 2003 June (Box-folder 10:9)
  - Commerce School, 2003 January - April (Box-folder 10:10)
  - Commonwealth Public Broadcasting Corporation, 2002 August - 2003 May (Box-folder 11:1)
  - Community Relations, 2002 November - 2003 March (Box-folder 11:2)
  - Condolences "A-L", 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 11:3)
  - Condolences "M-Z", 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 11:4)
  - Congress, 2002 August - 2003 June (Box-folder 11:5)
  - Continuing and Professional Studies, 2002 July - 2003 June (Box-folder 11:6)
  - Council for Higher Education Accreditation, 2003 May - June (Box-folder 11:7)
  - Council for Higher Education Accreditation, 2003 April 15 (Box-folder 11:8)
  - Council for Higher Education Accreditation, 2003 March - April 15 (Box-folder 12:1)
  - Council for Higher Education Accreditation, 2002 October - 2003 February (Box-folder 12:2)
  - Council for Higher Education Accreditation, 2002 September 16 (Box-folder 12:3)
  - Council for Higher Education Accreditation, 2002 July - September 12 (Box-folder 12:4)
  - Council of Presidents, 2003 March- June (Box-folder 12:5)
  - Council of Presidents, 2002 July - 2003 March (Box-folder 12:6)
  - Council on Competitiveness, 2002 June - 2003 June (Box-folder 13:1)
  - "Da" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 13:2)
  - "De-Do" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 13:3)
  - "Dr-Dy" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 13:4)
  - Darden School, 2002 July - 2003 June (Box-folder 13:5)
  - Development, 2002 November- 2003 June (Box-folder 13:6)
  - Development, 2002 October (Box-folder 13:7)
  - Development, 2002 September (Box-folder 13:8)
  - Development, 2002 July - August (Box-folder 14:1)
  - Drama, 2003 January (Box-folder 14:2)
  - "Ea-El" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 14:3)
  - "Em-Ez" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 14:4)
  - Economics, 2003 March (Box-folder 14:5)
  - Education School, 2002 June- 2003 May (Box-folder 14:6)
  - Engineering and Applied Sciences, 2002 July - 2003 June (Box-folder 14:7)
  - English, 2003 April - May (Box-folder 14:8)
  - Enrollment, 2003 March (Box-folder 14:9)
  - Environmental Sciences, 2002 November - 2003 April (Box-folder 14:10)
  - Equal Opportunity Office, 2002 July - 2003 January (Box-folder 14:11)
  - "Fa-Fi" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 14:12)
  - "Fl" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 14:13)
  - "Fo-Fu" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 15:1)
  - Facilities Management, 2002 July- 2003 March (Box-folder 15:2)
  - Faculty, 2002 September - 2003 May (Box-folder 15:3)
  - Fall Convocation, 2002 September-October (Box-folder 15:4)
  - Family Violence Prevention Fund, 2002 December (Box-folder 15:5)
  - Final Exercises, 2002 October- 2003 June (Box-folder 15:6)
  - Finance, 2002 October - 2003 June (Box-folder 15:7)
  - Financial Aid to Students, 2002 July - 2003 June (Box-folder 15:8)
  - Food Services (Dining Services - ARAMARK), 2003 March (Box-folder 15:9)
  - French Language and Literature, 2003 February (Box-folder 15:10)
  - "Ga-Ge" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 15:11)
  - "Gi-Gu" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 15:12)
  - General Assembly - General, 2003 January 16 - June (Box-folder 16:1)
  - General Assembly - General, 2003 January 3 - 9 (Box-folder 16:2)
  - General Assembly - General, 2002 July - December (Box-folder 16:3)
  - General Assembly - House, 2002 August (Box-folder 16:4)
  - General Council - General, 2003 June (Box-folder 16:5)
  - General Services (State), 2002 November (Box-folder 16:6)
  - Governmental Relations, 2002 November - 2003 June (Box-folder 16:7)
  - Governor's Office - General, 2003 April- June (Box-folder 16:8)
  - Governor's Office - General, 2002 July- 2003 March (Box-folder 16:9)
  - Governor's Office - Administration, 2002 July - September (Box-folder 17:1)
  - Governor's Office - Commerce and Trade, 2002 August (Box-folder 17:2)
  - Governor's Office - Education, 2003 March- July (Box-folder 17:3)
  - Governor's Office - Education, 2002 July - 2003 February (Box-folder 17:4)
  - Governor's Office - Finance, 2003 March (Box-folder 17:5)
  - Governor's Office - Public Safety and Transportation, 2003 June (Box-folder 17:6)
  - Governor's Office - Technology, 2003 January (Box-folder 17:7)
  - "Ha-He" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 17:8)
  - "Hi-Hn" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 17:9)
  - "Ho" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 17:10)
  - "Hu-Hy" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 18:1)
  - History, 2002 September - October (Box-folder 18:2)
  - Honor System/Committee, 2002 December - 2003 February (Box-folder 18:3)
  - Housing, 2002 July - 2003 April (Box-folder 18:4)
  - Human Resources, 2002 August - 2003 June (Box-folder 18:5)
  - "IBM-Ins" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 18:6)
  - "Int-It" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 18:7)
  - Information Technologies (UVA), 2003 April - May (Box-folder 18:8)
  - Institutional Assessment & Studies, 2002 September - 2003 May (Box-folder 18:9)
  - International Studies, 2002 July- 2003 June (Box-folder 18:10)
  - Invitations to Inaugurations "A-M", 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 18:11)
  - Invitations to Inaugurations "N-W", 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 19:1)
  - Invitations to Social Events "A-Y", 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 19:2)
  - "Ja-Je" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 19:3)
  - "Jo-Ju" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 19:4)
  - Jefferson Memorial Foundation, Thomas, 2002 December- 2003 June (Box-folder 19:5)
  - Jefferson Scholars Program, 2002 October- 2003 April (Box-folder 19:6)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission, 2002 July- 2003 June (Box-folder 19:7)
  - "K" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 20:1)
  - Keswick Club and Hall, 2002 July- 2003 May (Box-folder 20:2)
  - "La-Le" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 20:3)
  - "Li" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 20:4)
  - "Lo-Ly" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 20:5)
  - Law, School of, 2002 July- 2003 May (Box-folder 20:6)
  - Library, 2002 August- 2003 June (Box-folder 21:1)
  - London, 2002 September (Box-folder 21:2)
  - "Ma" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 21:3)
  - "Mc-Me" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 21:4)
  - "Mi-Mu" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 21:5)
  - Major Events Office, 2003 June (Box-folder 21:6)
  - Management and Budget, 2002 August-2003 June (Box-folder 21:7)
  - Mariners' Museum, 2003 February - May (Box-folder 22:1)
  - Mariners' Museum, 2002 December-2003 February (Box-folder 22:2)
  - Mariners' Museum, 2002 September - November (Box-folder 22:3)
  - Mariners' Museum, 2002 July - August (Box-folder 22:4)
  - Medical Center -General, 2002 July- 2003 May (Box-folder 22:5)
  - Medical Center- Hospital, 2002 July- 2003 May (Box-folder 22:6)
  - Medical Center-Medical School, 2002 July- 2003 May (Box-folder 22:7)
  - Medical Center- Nursing School, 2002 September-November (Box-folder 22:8)
  - Mellon Foundation, Andrew W., 2002 November- 2003 June (Box-folder 22:9)
  - Mount Graham Observatory, 2002 July- 2003 January (Box-folder 22:10)
  - Music, 2003 February - April (Box-folder 23:1)
  - "Nan-Nat" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 23:2)
  - "Nau-No" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 23:3)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges, 2002 August-2003 June (Box-folder 23:4)
  - National Institute of Alcohol Abuse and Alcoholism, 2002 October (Box-folder 23:5)
  - National Light Rail Initiative, 2003 (Box-folder 23:6)
  - National Science Foundation, 2002 July - 2003 June (Box-folder 23:7)
  - New York/Connecticut Visits, 2002 February (Box-folder 23:8)
  - "O" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 23:9)
  - Oak Ridge Associated Universities, 2002 August - November (Box-folder 23:10)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa, 2002 September - 2003 February (Box-folder 24:1)
  - Organizational Chart for the University of Virginia (oversize), 2002
  - Otley Hall, Suffolk, England, 2003 April - July (Box-folder 24:2)
  - "Pa-Pe" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 24:3)
  - "Pf-Po" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 24:4)
  - "Pr-Pu" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 24:5)
  - Parents Advisory Association, 2003 March (Box-folder 24:6)
  - Parking and Transportation, 2002 October- 2003 June (Box-folder 24:7)
  - Physics- Term Paper Plagiarism Scandal, 2002 November (Box-folder 24:8)
  - Politics, Department of, 2002 September- 2003 April (Box-folder 24:9)
  - President's Senior Cabinet, 2002 August- 2003 March (Box-folder 24:10)
  - Procurement Services, 2003 March (Box-folder 24:11)
  - Provost, 2002 September- 2003 June (Box-folder 25:1)
  - "Q-Ri" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 25:2)
  - "Ro-Ru" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 25:3)
  - Religious Studies, 2002 September - December (Box-folder 25:4)
  - Requests for Nominations "A-W", 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 25:5)
  - Research and Graduate Studies, 2002 August- 2003 June (Box-folder 25:6)
  - Reserve Officer Training Corps, 2002 September - 2003 May (Box-folder 25:7)
  - Rotunda Society, 2003 June (Box-folder 25:8)
  - "Sa-Se" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 26:1)
  - "Sh-Sn" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 26:2)
  - "So" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 26:3)
  - "Sp-St" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 26:4)
  - "Su-Sy" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 26:5)
  - Sallie Mae, 2003 May (Box-folder 27:1)
  - Sallie Mae, 2003 February - April (Box-folder 27:2)
  - Sallie Mae, 2003 January (Box-folder 27:3)
  - Sallie Mae, 2002 August- November (Box-folder 27:4)
  - Senate Faculty (University), 2002 December - 2003 April (Box-folder 27:5)
  - Small, Albert, 2002 August - 2003 June (Box-folder 27:6)
  - Sociology, 2003 January (Box-folder 27:7)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 2002 September - 2003 January (Box-folder 28:1)
  - Southern Regional Education Board, 2002 September - 2003 March (Box-folder 28:2)
  - Sponsored Programs, 2002 November- 2003 February (Box-folder 28:3)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV), 2003 April- June (Box-folder 28:4)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV), 2003 March 25 (Box-folder 28:5)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV), 2003 February - March 19 (Box-folder 28:6)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV), 2002 September - 2003 January (Box-folder 28:7)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV), 2002 September-October (Box-folder 28:8)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV), 2002 June -August (Box-folder 29:1)
  - State Department of Education, 2002 December- 2003 March (Box-folder 29:2)
  - Student Affairs - General, 2003 April - June (Box-folder 29:3)
  - Student Affairs - General, 2003 March (Box-folder 29:4)
  - Student Affairs - General, 2002 August - 2003 February (Box-folder 29:5)
  - Student Affairs - Dean of Students Office, 2002 November- 2003 June (Box-folder 29:6)
  - Student Affairs - Fraternities and Sororities, 2003 January - April (Box-folder 29:7)
  - Student Council, 2002 July - 2003 April (Box-folder 29:8)
  - Summer Session, 2003 January - April (Box-folder 29:9)
  - "Ta-Th" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 29:10)
  - "Ti-Ty" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 29:11)
  - "Ud-Unit" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 29:12)
  - "Univ-Ut" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 30:1)
  - United States Department of Education, 2002 August - 2003 May (Box-folder 30:2)
  - United Way/Combined Charitable Campaign, 2002 August - 2003 April (Box-folder 30:3)
  - Universities Research Association, 2002 September - 2003 January (Box-folder 30:4)
  - University of Virginia Press, 2002 September - 2003 June (Box-folder 30:5)
  - University of Virginia's College at Wise, 2002 September - 2003 May (Box-folder 30:6)
  - University Relations/News Office, 2002 September - December (Box-folder 30:7)
  - "Va-Virginia D" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 30:8)
  - 2002 - 2003, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 31:1)
  - Vice President's Retreat, 2002 August (Box-folder 31:2)
  - Vice President's Retreat, 2002 August (Box-folder 31:3)
  - Virginia 2020, 2003 February - March (Box-folder 31:4)
  - Virginia 2020, 2002 September (Box-folder 31:5)
  - Virginia Business Higher Education Council, 2002 October - 2003 January (Box-folder 31:6)
  - Virginia Festival of American Film, 2002 August - 2003 March (Box-folder 32:1)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review, 2002 July - 2003 April (Box-folder 32:2)
  - Virginia Student Aid Foundation, 2002 October (Box-folder 32:3)
  - "Wa-We" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 32:4)
  - "Wh-Wy" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 32:5)
  - Weldon Cooper Center for Public Service, 2002 December - 2003 June (Box-folder 32:6)
  - Woodrow Wilson National Fellowship Foundation, 2002 August - 2003 June (Box-folder 32:7)
  - "Y-Z" Miscellaneous, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 32:8)
- Series II: Seldom Used Permanent Files
  - Alumni Association - Arts & Sciences Emeritus Society, 1992 May - 1997 June (Box-folder 32:9)
  - Alumni Association - Inventor of the Year Award, 1991 June- 1995 November (Box-folder 32:10)
  - Alumni Association - Law, 1987 December - 1996 May (Box-folder 32:11)
  - Alumni Association - Nursing, 1975 August - 1996 June (Box-folder 33:1)
  - Alumni Council of College and Graduate School, 1996 May - 1999 September (Box-folder 33:2)
  - Alumni Council of College & Graduate School, 1994 June - 1996 March (Box-folder 33:3)
  - Alumni Council of College and Graduate School, 1992 May - 1994 April (Box-folder 33:4)
  - Alumni - Distinguished Student Award, 1973 March - 1997 January (Box-folder 33:5)
  - Alumni - Medical Advisory Committee, 1974 August - 2000 February (Box-folder 33:6)
  - Cabell Hall Mural, 1997 April - June (Box-folder 33:7)
  - Cabell Hall Mural, 1996 February - 1997 March (Box-folder 34:1)
  - Visitors, Board of, 2002 May - June (Box-folder 34:2)
  - Visitors, Board of, 2002 March - April (Box-folder 34:3)
  - Visitors, Board of, 2002 January - February (Box-folder 34:4)
  - Visitors, Board of, 2001 October - December (Box-folder 34:5)
  - Visitors, Board of, 2001 January, July - September (Box-folder 34:6)
- Series III: Restricted Files
  - "A" Miscellaneous Restricted Files, pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 35:1)
  - Admissions - General, pulled from general files, 2003 April- June (Box-folder 35:2)
  - Admissions - General, pulled from general files, 2003 February- March (Box-folder 35:3)
  - Admissions - General, pulled from general files, 2002 December - 2003 January (Box-folder 35:4)
  - Admissions - General, pulled from general files, 2002 October - November (Box-folder 35:5)
  - Admissions - General, pulled from general files, 2002 July- September (Box-folder 35:6)
  - Admission - Law School, pulled from general files, 2002 October - 2003 March (Box-folder 36:1)
  - Applications for Positions "A-W", pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 36:2)
  - "B" Miscellaneous Restricted Files, pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 36:3)
  - "C-D" Miscellaneous Restricted Files, pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 36:4)
  - Condolences - Restricted "A-W", pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 36:5)
  - "E-H" Miscellaneous Restricted Files, pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 36:6)
  - Gifts & Grants "A-Be", pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 36:7)
  - Gifts & Grants "Bi-Br", pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 37:1)
  - Gifts & Grants "Bu-Cl", pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 37:2)
  - Gifts & Grants "Co-Da", pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 37:3)
  - Gifts & Grants "De-Du", pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 37:4)
  - Gifts & Grants "E-Fl", pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 37:5)
  - Gifts & Grants "Fo-Fu", pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 37:6)
  - Gifts & Grants "Ga-Go", pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 38:1)
  - Gifts & Grants "Gr-Ha", pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 38:2)
  - Gifts & Grants "He-I", pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 38:3)
  - Gifts & Grants "J-Ki", pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 38:4)
  - Gifts & Grants "Kl-L", pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 38:5)
  - Gifts & Grants "Ma-Mc", pulled from general files, 2002 - 2003 (Box-folder 38:6)